watchesonnet.com 2012-11-03

# Privacy & Security | WatchesOnNet.com

**ABOUT THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT**

We gather information from you when you create an account our site, order an item on our site, subscribe to receive emails from us, respond to a questionnaire or complete a form. When you place an order on our site, or create an account on our site, you may be asked to enter one or more of the following details: your name, your email address, your mailing address, your phone number, your credit card information. Note that you are able to visit our website anonymously.

**WHY WE REQUIRE INFORMATION FROM YOU**

1\. Transaction Processing We will never sell, exchange, transfer, or give any other company for any reason whatsoever your public or private information without your consent, for any reason other than to deliver the product or service you have purchased.

2\. Email Delivery Note We will only use the email address you provide for order processing to send you updates and information regarding your order. If you have signed up for our email newsletter, you can at any time unsubscribe from receiving future emails. If you would like to unsubscribe, instructions are provided at the footer of these emails.

**SECURITY MEASURES WE TAKE TO PROTECT YOUR INFORMATION**

The personal information you provide when you place an order on our site, or when you enter, submit or access your personal information is information that we keep safe by implementing a variety of security measures. We provide the use of a secure server. All payment information that you supply is transmitted through Secure Socket Layer, or SSL, technology. That information is then encrypted into our Payment gateway provider's database which is only accessible to designated authorized persons who have received special access rights to such systems, and who are required to maintain strict confidentiality of all information at all times. Your credit card information is never stored on our servers after a transaction.

**USE OF COOKIES**

Cookies are very small files that a website or website providers transfer to a user’s computer’s hard drive through the user’s web browser, if the user allows cookies, in order to enable the website or website’s provider’s systems to identify the user’s browser and capture and recall specific information. Our website uses cookies to compile aggregate data in regards to website traffic and site interaction so in the future we can offer a better site experience and tools to our users. We also use cookies to help process and remember the items in a user’s shopping cart. While we may also contract with third-party service providers to help us better understand our site visitors, these providers are only permitted to use the information they collect on our behalf to help us improve and conduct our business. Note that your computer has the option to warn you each time a cookie is being sent, as well as the option to turn off cookies through your browser settings. In the event that you turn off cookies, some services may not work properly. If this should happen you can contact us to place an order or to receive any other services.

**INFORMATION DISCLOSURE**

We do not transfer in any way, including through a sale or trade, your personally identifiable information to any outside party, other than trusted third parties who help us with website operation, business management, or customer service, and all of whom agree to keeping all your personally identifiable information strictly confidential at all time. We may also disclose your information when we believe disclosure is suitable to enforce site policies, comply with the law, or to protect the rights, property or safety of ourselves or others. Note that we may provide other parties with non-personally identifiable visitor information for uses such as marketing and advertising.

**EXTERNAL LINKS**

Third party products or services that may be included on our website, as per our discretion, have independent and separate privacy policies, and we are therefore not responsible or liable for the activities and content of these external sites. At the same time, we do aim to protect our website’s integrity and encourage feedback in regards to these sites.

**CALIFORNIA ONLINE PRIVACY PROTECTION ACT**

****We comply with the California Online Privacy Protection Act, and therefore do not distribute your personal information to external parties without your consent. In compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all site users have the capabilities to make any changes to their information at any given time by simply logging into their account page and editing their profile and settings.

**CHILDREN’S ONLINE PRIVACY PROTECTION ACT**

We also comply with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act, or COPPA, and therefore do not gather any information from anyone under the age of 13. Our products, services and website are all aimed at people 13 years and older.

**TERMS AND CONDITIONS**

We encourage you to read our terms and conditions, which establishes the limitations of liability, disclaimers and use of our website.

**YOUR CONSENT**

In the act of using our site, you agree with our website Privacy Policy.

**PRIVACY POLICY MODIFICATIONS**

Any changes in our privacy policy will be posted here on this page.

**HOW TO CONTACT US**

For questions regarding this policy, please feel free to contact us
